

ACADEMIC TRAINING

National University Autonomous of Mexico

Intern Electrical Engineering Electronics specialty Control Systems

Computer Superior School National Polytechnic Institute

Fifth semester of Systems Engineering Computational. (Truncated)

Diploma Course Linux Servers Interlegit

Diploma focused on installation and configuration of a GNU / Linux server making use of shell scripting.

LANGUAGES

- English B2 level
- **Basic French**
- **Native Spanish**

ARMANDO ARCINIEGA SOLANO

Electrical Electronic Engineer Web Developer Systems Administrator

- **GNU/Linux Server** Administration
- Laravel and Vue basics
- CSS Pre Processos LESS and SASS
- **Relational database** development with MvSOL
- Web Development(PHP, HTML5 Bootstrap, CSS, Javascript)
- Version Control with git under Github and Bitbucket

PROFILE

Front End Web Developer

Advanced knowledge in PHP, HTML5, CSS and JavaScript

Advanced knowledge in Bootstrap.

Experience with Laravel and blade templetes

Vue basics

API Rest. fetch basics

Open Graph meta-tags and SEO basics

Design and implementation of relational databases with MySQL, advanced intermediate level

Intermediate experience in other programming languages as C, Java, Python, Shell Scripting.

Knowledge in administration and experience in managing work teams

Sales and marketing experience

Ease of speech and communication

Excellent presentation and assertiveness

I am a dynamic, positive, proactive and outgoing person

OTHER SKILLS

Experience in service, installation and maintenance of Networking infrastructure

Equipment configuration (Servers, switching, access point)

Low-voltage electrical installations

Arduino Basics

CONTACT





Work Experience

SYSTEMS MANAGER

IMEF S.A. de C.V

May 2014- August 2015

Commissioning, maintenance and operation of computer equipment (PC / LapTop).

Servers (Windows Server 2008, Linux Ubuntu Server). LAN networks.

Video surveillance equipment configuration, among other activities related to remote access to servers in the company.

SYSTEMS MANAGER

Víctor Montes y Asociados

October 2015- August 2016

Maintenance and assembly of computer equipment (Laptop, Desktop and Printers).

Creation of company web pages (CSS, HTML5, MySQL, PHP). LAN networks.

Databases (MvSql).

Configuration and use of software in general.

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER IR

Kiwinet

October 2017- April 2018

Creation and layout of websites with HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap 3, and PHP. Design and implementation of relational databases with MySql. Basics Search Engine Optimization (SEO).

Ubuntu Server, Apache.

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER JR

Web de Cero

January 2019- June 2019

Creation and layout of websites with HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap 4, and PHP. Laravel Basics.(Blade Templetes, Routes, Migrations, MVC)

lavaScript(iQuery)

LESS and SASS CCS's preprocessors

Composer and npm

Ubuntu Server, Apache2, Prepros, VSCode, FileZilla, SSH, SAMBA, SHELL Scripting Git(BitBucket, Git-Hub, Git Cracken).

MUNICIPAL COMPUTER SUPPORT, CENSUS 2020

INEGI

January 2020- May 2020

Management and implementation of computer resources of the Institute attached to the municipality of Tonanitla at the East Mexico State Coordination.

Personnel management and reporting.

Courses

CCNA 1. Networking Basics.

CCNA 2.Router and Routing Basics.

CCNA 3. Switching Basics and Intermediate Routing.

CCNA 4 .WAN Technologies.

Not certificate yet

*Web Asistant

*Data Curator

At:

https://capacitateparaelempleo.org/ Fundación Carlos Slim

Linux Servers Diploma